New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides; Records apap151
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- NYCAP Publications - Other, 1981-2002; 6; 16.33 cubic ft.
  - Subseries 1: NYCAP Publications, Undated; 6.1
    - ECO-Politics/New York League of Conservation Voters, 1994-2000 (Box 15 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - Hudson Valley Green Times, 1989-1990 (Box 15 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - Hudson Valley Green Times, 1990-1992 (Box 15 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - Human Ecology Action League, New York City Chapter/New York City HEAL Newsletter, 1997; 2000 (Box 15 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - TERRA News, 1990-1993 (Box 15 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
  - Subseries 2: Other Publications, Undated; 6.2
    - A Consumer's Guide to Natural Organic Ecological Landscapers, NYCAP, 1993 (Box 1 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - NYCAP Brochures and Pamphlets, 2001; Undated (Box 1 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - NYCAP News, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - NYCAP News, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - NYCAP News, 1992 (Box 1 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - NYCAP News, 1993 (Box 1 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - NYCAP News, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 1)
    - NYCAP News, 1994 (Box 2 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 2)
    - NYCAP News, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 3)
    - Professional Solutions/Combating Cockroaches, Undated (Box 2 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 4)
    - Quick Solutions, 1997 (Box 2 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 5)
    - Solutions, 1996 (Box 2 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 6)
    - Solutions News, 1998-2002 (Box 2 (6-NYCAP Publications - Other), Folder 7)
- Pesticide and Pest Information, 1977-2000; 7; 12.44 cubic ft.
  This series contains mostly materials that NYCAP collected for its information clearinghouse. It consists primarily of photocopies of the work of others, on specific pesticides and pests. It has been divided up into two subseries, one for pesticides, and the other for pests. Two important sources of the pesticides information were the EPA Fact Sheets and the Extension Toxicology Network (EXTOXNET). The amount of material on each pesticide or pest ranges from a page or two to an entire linear foot on mosquitoes.
  Arranged alphabetically by specific pesticide or pest.
  - Subseries 1: Pests, Undated; 7.1
    - Ants and Carpenter Ants, Informational Packet, 1988-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 1)
    - Ants, Argentine Ants, 2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 2)
    - Ants, Carpenter Ants, 1985-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 3)
    - Ants- Control Methods, 1993-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 4)
    - Ants, Fire Ants, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 5)
    - Aphids, General Information, 1984-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 6)
    - Aphids, Information Packet, 1989-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 7)
    - Bats, Information on Bat Control and Using Them to Control Insects, 1984-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 8)
    - Bats, Information Packet, 1984-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 9)
    - Bagworms, General Information, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 10)
    - Bees, Africanized Honey Bee, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 11)
    - Bees, Benefits of, 1993-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 12)
    - Bees, Carpenter Bees, 1990-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 13)
    - Bees, Honey Bees, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 14)
    - Bees and Other Stinging Insects, Pesticides, 1987-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 15)
    - Bees and Other Stinging Insects, Resources for IPM, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 16)
    - Bees and Other Stinging Insects, Stings and Venom, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 17)
    - Bees and Other Stinging Insects, Various Articles, 1979-1998 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 18)
    - Bees and Pesticides, Quick Solutions Draft, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 19)
    - Beetles: Asian Long-horned Beetle, General Information, 1996-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 20)
    - Beetles: Carpet Beetles, Information Packet, 1991 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 21)
    - Beetles: Cucumber Beetles, Information Packet, 1991-1998 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 22)
    - Beetles, General Information, 1986-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 23)
    - Beetles: Japanese Beetles, Control Methods, 1989-1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 24)
    - Beetles: Leafy Spurge (Flea Beetle), Article, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 25)
    - Beetles: Wood-boring Beetle, Information Packet, 1985-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 26)
    - Bedbugs, Information Packet, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 27)
    - Big-eyed Bugs, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 28)
    - Birch Leaf Miner, Fact Sheet, 1994 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 29)
    - Birds, Geese, 1993-2001; Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 30)
    - Birds, General, 1984-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 31)
    - Birds, Information Packet, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 32)
    - Birds, Woodpeckers, Information Packet, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 33)
    - Black Spot on Roses, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 34)
    - Black Vine Weevils, Information Packet, 1991 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 35)
    - Boxelder Bugs, Information Packet, 1987-2002 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 36)
    - Brown Marmorated Stink Bugs, 2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 37)
    - Cankerworms (Inchworms), General Information, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 38)
    - Caterpillars, General Information, 1984-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 39)
    - Centipedes, Information Packet, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 40)
    - Chestnut Blight, Article, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 41)
    - Chiggers, General Information, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 42)
    - Chinch Bugs, Information Packet, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 43)
    - Cicadas, General Information, 1990 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 44)
    - Cockroach Control Methods, 1981; 1983; 1991; 1995; Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 45)
    - Cockroaches, General Information, 1981-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 46-47)
    - Cockroaches, German Cockroaches, 1984-1992 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 48)
    - Cockroaches, Information Packet, 1991-2002 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 49)
    - Cockroaches, NYS Department of Labor Grant Project, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 50)
    - Common Household Invaders, Information Packet, 1990-1995 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 51)
    - Crickets, General Information, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 52)
    - Crickets, Information Packet, 1991-1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 53)
    - Deer, 1994-2002 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 54)
    - Dutch Elm Disease, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 55)
    - Earwigs, Information Packet, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 56)
    - European Corn Borers, Articles, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 57)
    - European Hornets, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 58)
    - "Fabric Eaters", Information Packet, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 59)
    - Flea Beetles Research and News Clippings, 1950; 1967-1973; 1978; 1981-1988; Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 60)
    - Fleas, Control Methods, 1980-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 61)
    - Fleas, Informational Packet, 1986-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 62)
    - Fleas, Safe Home Digest, "Safe Flea Control", 1991 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 63)
    - Fleas, Sample Packet, "Safe Flea Control", 1980-1993 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 64)
    - Flies, General Information, 1978-2002 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 65)
    - Flies, Information Packet, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 66)
    - Flies: Cluster Flies, Information Packet, 1991-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 67)
    - Flies: Black Flies, General Information, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 68)
    - Flies: Drain Flies, General Information, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 69)
    - Flies: Filth Flies, General Information, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 70)
    - Flies: Fruit Flies, Information Packet, 1991-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 71)
    - Flies: Mediterranean Fruit Fly, Eradication and Health Risks, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 72)
    - Flies: Mediterranean Fruit Fly, General Information, 1995 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 73)
    - Flying Animals Pest Control Methods, 1991-1992; 1995 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 74)
    - Fungus, General Information, 1998-1999 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 75)
    - Fungus Gnats, Information Packet, 1991-1996 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 76)
    - Gophers, General Information, 2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 77)
    - Grasshopper, Control Methods, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 78)
    - Grubs, Information Packet, 1989-2001 (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 79)
    - Hemlock Wooley Adelgid, Information Packet, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 80)
    - Household Pests, Alternatives to Pesticides, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 81)
    - Household Pests, Least-Toxic Control Summaries, Undated (Box 1 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 82)
    - Household Pests, Quick Reference Pest Control Guide, Undated (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 1)
    - Household Pests, Safe Household Pest Control Information Packet, 1988-1996 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 2)
    - Insect Management Procedures, 1986-1988; 1991; 1993-1995 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 3)
    - Insect Management Resource Guides, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 4)
    - Japanese Beetles and General Information Packet, 1991 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 5)
    - Ladybugs, General Information, 1990-2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 6)
    - Lice Booklet, 1997 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 7)
    - Lice, General Information, 1990-2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 8)
    - Lice, National Pediculosis Association, 1985-1997 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 9)
    - Locust, Control Methods, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 10)
    - Mice, 1984-2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 11)
    - Mice and Rat Control Methods, 1986-2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 12)
    - Mice, Information Packet, 1990-2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 13)
    - Midges, General Information, 1997-2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 14)
    - Milfoil, Safer Controls for Euraslan Milfoil Information Packet, 1997 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 15)
    - Milky Disease Spore, Biological Control, Undated (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 16)
    - Mites: Dust Mites, General Information, 1970-1999 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 17)
    - Mites, Information Packet, 1990-1997 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 18)
    - Moles, Information Packet, 1989-1996 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 19)
    - Mosquito Control, Advocacy and Outreach Contact Information, 1999 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 20)
    - Mosquito Control, Albany County Meeting on Spraying, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 21)
    - Mosquito Control, Albany County West Nile Virus, Articles, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 22)
    - Mosquito Control, Amherst (NY), 1992-1996; Undated (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 23)
    - Mosquito Control, Articles re: Spraying, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 24)
    - Mosquito Control, Cattaraugus County, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 25)
    - Mosquito Control, Challenge to Aerial Pesticide Spraying, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 26)
    - Mosquito Control, Cicero Swamp/ Eastern Equine Encephalitis (EEE) (1 of 2), 1989-1994 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 27)
    - Mosquito Control, Comments of NYS Attorney General Spitzer on West Nile Encephalitis Response Plan, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 28)
    - Mosquito Control, Commonly Used Pesticides, Several Information Packets, 1987-1999 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 29)
    - Mosquito Control, Dutchess County, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 30)
    - Mosquito Control, Eastern Equine Encephalitis (EEE), 1990-1998 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 31)
    - Mosquito Control, Fish and Wildlife Related Impacts of Pesticides, New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 32)
    - Mosquito Control, General Articles re: West Nile Virus, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 33)
    - Mosquito Control, Ineffectiveness of Spraying, 2000-2002 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 34)
    - Mosquito Control, IPM, 1984-1996; Undated (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 35)
    - Mosquito Control, John and Saundra Garofalo Spraying Incident, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 36)
    - Mosquito Control, Letters re: malathion, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 37)
    - Mosquito Control, Long Island, 1989-1994 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 38)
    - Mosquito Control, Malathion use in New York City, 1990-1999 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 39)
    - Mosquito Control, Massachusetts Audubon Society, 1990-1993 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 40)
    - Mosquito Control, Nature Conservancy, 1989-1993 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 41)
    - Mosquito Control, New Jersey, 2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 42)
    - Mosquito Control, New York City Department of Health, Environmental Impact Statement re: Mosquito Control Plan, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 43)
    - Mosquito Control, New York City Department of Health, Press Releases, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 44)
    - Mosquito Control, New York City Spraying, Articles, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 45)
    - Mosquito Control, New York State Attorney General, Letter to Mayor Giuliani, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 46)
    - Mosquito Control, News Articles re: West Nile Virus in New York City, 2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 47)
    - Mosquito Control, No Spray Coalition, 2001 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 48)
    - Mosquito Control, NYCAP Position Paper, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 49)
    - Mosquito Control Pesticides, 1996-2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 50)
    - Mosquito Control, Pro-DDT Letter and NYCAP Response, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 51)
    - "Mosquito Control Projects in Massachusetts: A Call for Change in Our Government", Gloria Black, 1993 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 52)
    - Mosquito Control, Response of Organizations to Department of Health West Nile Virus Plan, 2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 53)
    - Mosquito Control, Rockland County Department of Health re: West Nile Virus, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 54)
    - Mosquito Control, Saratoga Springs, 1991-1995 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 55)
    - Mosquito Control, Spraying Correspondence and Advocacy, 1999 (Box 2 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 56)
    - Mosquito Control, State of Connecticut West Nile Virus Surveillance and Response Plan, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 1)
    - Mosquito Control, Statements by NY Municipalities re: Spraying, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 2)
    - Mosquito Control, Town of Amherst Homeowner's Pamphlet, Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 3)
    - Mosquito Control, Upstate New York Spraying, News Clippings, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 4)
    - Mosquito Control, West Nile Spraying Schedules, New York (and surrounding areas), 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 5)
    - Mosquito Control, Westchester County Department of Health News Release re: West Nile Virus, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 6)
    - Mosquito, Adirondack Communities Against Aerial Pesticides, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 7-8)
    - Mosquitoes, General Information, 1972-2002 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 9)
    - Mosquitoes, Information Packet, 1984-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 10)
    - Mosquitoes, NYCAP Mosquito Position Paper, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 11)
    - Mosquitoes, Partnership for Safe Mosquito Management, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 12)
    - Mosquitoes, Repellants, 1977-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 13)
    - Mosquitoes, Saratoga County Pesticide Use, 1990-2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 14)
    - Mosquitoes, West Nile Virus, 2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 15)
    - Moths (Clothes), Information Packet, 1986-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 16)
    - Moths (Clothes), NYCAP Information Packet and Other Articles, 1986-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 17)
    - Moths (Gypsy), Control Methods, 1981-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 18)
    - Moths (Gypsy), Information Packet, 1989-1994 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 19)
    - Moths (Meal), Control, 1985-2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 20)
    - Moths (Meal and Pantry), Information Packet, 1986-2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 21)
    - Nematodes, General Information, 1997-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 22)
    - Onion Maggots, 1999 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 23)
    - Peach Tree Borer, Information Packet, 1991-1997 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 24)
    - Potato Lake Blight, General Information, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 25)
    - Rats, 1970-1992; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 26)
    - Rats, Control Methods, 1984-1986 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 27)
    - Rats, Information Packet, 1989-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 28)
    - Rats and Mice: IPM for Schools, Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 29)
    - Rodents, 1993-2002 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 30)
    - Rodents, Materials for Proposed Information Packet(s), 1989-1997 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 31-32)
    - Scabies Mites, Information Packet, 1991-2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 33)
    - Scale Insects, General Information, 1991-1997 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 34)
    - Scorpions, General Information, Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 35)
    - Silverfish, General Information, 1990; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 36)
    - Silverfish, Information Packet, Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 37)
    - Skunks, Information Packet, 1990-2000 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 38)
    - Slugs and Snails, Information Packet, 1980-2000; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 39)
    - Snakes, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 40)
    - Spiders, General Information, 1989-1995 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 41)
    - Spiders, Information Packet, 1991 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 42)
    - Squirrels and Chipmunks, 1992-1999; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 43)
    - Stored Product Pesticides, General Information, 1986-1996 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 44)
    - Termites, Articles, 1984-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 45-46)
    - Termites, Baiting Systems, 1994-1997 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 47)
    - Termites, Fumex, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 48)
    - Termites, Information Packet, 1988-2001 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 49)
    - Termites, School IPM Packets, Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 50)
    - Thrips, 1997-1999 (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 51)
    - Ticks, Deer, Chemical Control and Opposition to Chemical Control, 1990-1993; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 52)
    - Ticks, Deer, Damminix, 1989-1994; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 53)
    - Ticks, Deer, Lyme Disease, 1988-2002; Undated (Box 3 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 54)
    - Ticks, General, 1984-1997 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 1)
    - Ticks, Information Packet, 1990-2000 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 2)
    - Varoa Mites, 1997-2000 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 3)
    - Vertebrates, 1992-2002; Undated (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 4-5)
    - Vine Mealy Bug, 1998 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 6)
    - Wasps, Digger Wasps, 1994 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 7)
    - Wasps, Paper Wasps, 1996 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 8)
    - Weevils, 1997; 2001 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 9)
    - Whiteflies, 1997; 2001 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 10)
    - Wildlife Repellants, 1999-2000 (Box 4 (7-Pesticide and Pest Information), Folder 11)